HER COMMENT IS UNIMAGINABLY
STUPID, OFFENSIVE, AND DANGEROUS.
THE RAID SHE'S TALKING ABOUT IN
CHICAGO WAS A BRILLIANTLY
EXECUTED RAID AGAINST A TRAIN
DE ARAGUA COMPLEX FILLED WITH
TDA TERRORISTS.
IT'S ONE OF THE MOST SUCCESSFUL
LAW ENFORCEDING OPERATIONS THAT
WE'VE SEEN IN THIS COUNTRY.
AS YOU KNOW, LAURA, TRAIN DE
ARAGUA IS RESPONSIBLE FOR SOME
OF THE MOST GRUESOME, HEINOUS
CRIMES THAT HAVE OCCURRED DURING
THE BIDEN ADMINISTRATION, LIKE
THE VICIOUS SEXUAL ASSAULT,
KIDNAPPING, AND SLAUGHTER OF
JOSELYN NUNGARY OR THE STONE-COLD
BUTCHERING OF LAKEN RILEY.
SO THESE ICE OFFICERS, THESE HEROES
SAVED GOD KNOWS HOW MANY LIVES BY
GETTING THESE TDA SCUM OUT OF
OUR COUNTRY.
PENDING THE LIVES, BY THE WAY, OF
EVERY SINGLE PERSON IN THAT
BUILDING.
A TRULY REMARKABLE OPERATION,
LAURA.
STEVEN, GOVERNOR PRISKER IS VERY
UPSET THAT YOU ALL AREN'T GOING
AFTER THE REAL PROBLEMS.
WHY?